Directed by
- Are you okay?
- What? Sure, carry on!
Come on.
Okay, now make it reappear
so we can have a drink.
Cheers.
WINTER BROTHERS
Hello?
Open the door.
I'm not leaving.
Open the door!
Do you want me to break the
window?
You don't have to pay all of it.
Okay, you don't have to pay.
We'll trade!
What would I do with that?
You can have my watch.
- Let's see it.
- It's right here.
It doesn't work.
It's dead. I can't hear
anything.
It just needs a new battery.
It's a fine watch.
If you change the battery,
it'll work just fine.
Nah, I don't know
Do you have anything else?
- Anything for a girl?
- Yes.
- I have all sorts of things for a girl.
- Like what?
- Kitchen knives.
- Seriously...
- I have all sorts of stuff.
- An old watch and kitchen knives?
If you put a new battery in it,
then...
Anything for a really beautiful
girl? You know, a girlfriend.
I have all sorts of things
for a beautiful girl.
- Never mind.
- I have...
- I have clothes for her. Move over.
I have it right here.
Yes...
No.
A military jacket.
For a girl?
Well, then...
Uhm, is...
Is that a shotgun?
What? The rifle?
It's a semi-automatic... M1.
It's air-cooled and with an
8-shot clip.
The clip is ejected with a
click.
Well, it's more like a pling.
Come watch this.
I just found it. Thanks.
What is it?
- What is it?
- Hang on.
Come push it down.
Again.
Time to go.
Let's have some.
Hey!
- What's in this?
- What?
- What's it made from?
- Pussy Juice.
- Oh?
I thought we were
drinking your piss.
Hey! Don't ever let me catch you
doing that again! Understood?
- What's the problem?
- What?
What? What are you talking
about?
Do that crap on your own time!
- Get to work! Daddy's boy.
- I'm not a daddy's boy!
- What?
- I'm not a daddy's boy.
- Get to work already!
- I don't have a dad.
What are you talking about?
I can't be a daddy's boy
when I don't have a dad.
What?
- It's hopeless.
- What?
- Never mind.
- Come on! There's plenty to do.
- I won't shit on the floor.
- What?
- I won't take a shit on the floor!
- Why not?
- You would just do it!
- Of course!
- Put your dick back in your pants.
- Why?
Because normal people
are staring at you.
Good morning.
I said good morning.
Aren't we going with you guys?
Get him, for fuck's sake!
Go!
Come on!
Emil!
Those are my panties!
Get off me.
Get off!
What's your plan?
- Plan? What plan?
- What are you gonna do?
Nothing. What am I supposed to
do?
Wait what do you mean?
It's becoming a problem.
Fix it.
Fix what? I have no idea
what you're talking about.
- You don't know?
- Know what?
- The thing with Michael.
- What's up with him?
- He's sick.
- What does that have to do with me?
They think your booze made him
sick.
Who's 'they'?
- Why do they think that?
- People talk.
People? Who? Why is someone saying
that he's sick from my booze?
- We all drink it all the time!
- I'm just saying what I've heard.
- From whom?
- I told you! People!
Why are you acting so weird?
Who are you?
- Who am I?
- Yes, and who's side are you on?
- I ask you, but you brush me off!
- Anna told me.
Fuck you, I'm just trying to
help!
Why are you always so fucking
difficult?
Can't you just be normal
like everyone else?
Why would I?
You're my brother and you love
me.
Why should I be like everyone
else?
Not like everyone else.
Just more relaxed
and less dark and aggressive.
- Dark and aggressive?
- Yeah. You are dark sometimes.
- Everyone has a little darkness in them.
- No, they don't.
- Yes, they do.
- No.
- Yes.
- I don't.
Yes, you do, you're just
too boring to know it.
You know what your problem is?
You don't like anyone.
You don't like people.
Johan, I am a person.
How can I not like myself?
No really,
how can one not like oneself?
Want some?
Why not?
- Why not?
- I don't have any money.
- You can borrow.
- No.
- You can borrow!
- Do you want one?
- No.
- Why not?
- I just don't want it.
What's going on with the light?
Hey, asshole!
Stop pointing
Hey! Carl wants to see you
upstairs!
Me? Why?
Now!
- You're Emil?
- Yes.
It's nice to meet you.
How long have you been with us?
I'm not exactly sure, about 5-7
years.
- 5-7? That's a lot.
- Yes.
That's a long time.
- And you're happy and satisfied?
- I'm okay, yeah.
That's good.
Where do you see yourself in
let's just say 5-7 years?
I don't know working here,
maybe?
Children?
Uhm, I don't know.
Maybe.
- So you do have a girlfriend?
- Yes.
- Is she beautiful?
- What?
Is your girlfriend beautiful?
Yes, she's very beautiful.
'Cause you're not
very good-looking yourself.
Or are you?
Do you think
you're a good-looking boy?
Okay. So you want to work here
for the next 5-7 years -
and have a child with a beautiful
girl and be happy and content.
Can I write that?
- Write?
- Hm?
"Emil wants to work
here in the factory
for at least 5-7 years more.
He wants a child with a beautiful
girl, and more than anything -
- he wants to be happy and
content."
"... happy and content."
How does that sound? Good?
Are you a thief, Emil?
No, I'm not.
Then why does this report
state you're a thief?
I don't know. I don't know
anything about a report.
Then read it.
It says three things.
First, that your name is Emil.
Secondly, that you're a thief.
And thirdly, that you've worked
hard for us for 5-7 years -
and want a child with a
beautiful girl
and want to be a happy and
content boy.
Can I go now?
Homebrew.
Did we forget something in the
report? Did we?
Hand me the report.
Peter.
Thank you, Peter.
Post scriptum.
"I steal chemicals
from the factory I work in.
I brew toxic liquor
and sell it to my co-workers."
Plus...
"I'm a murderer."
Is this some sort of joke?
You didn't know?
One of my best employees is dying
in the hospital as we speak.
Because of your brew.
Is that a joke?
Do you think I'm joking?
You're not going to drink with
me?
One little drink won't kill you.
But the whole bottle might.
Are you awake?
I want you, Emil.
I want you, too.
I want to eat you.
Would you like me to eat you?
Yes.
- Say 'yes, please'.
- Yes, please.
Would you like to eat me?
Yes.
I want to eat you.
I want to be loved and fucked.
I love you.
I'm yours.
I will love and fuck you all day
- every day for the rest of your
life.
Do you love me?
Yes.
Thank you.
Don't. I'm sleeping.
Good night.
I said good night.
Hey.
Stop.
Stop it.
Come on, stop.
I hate you!
Calm down!
She was mine!
Emil.
Emil?
Emil...
Hey... hey!
Emil!
Emil, come on...
Come on!
Emil!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry...
Emil!
What's up?
I'd like to buy a bottle.
I'm going to tell you a story.
Okay?
So listen up.
It's about a man, who worked
here years ago, and his dog.
It's a true story,
and it happened right here.
Probably before you were born.
So this man had a dog.
His wife hated dogs.
She hated all animals,
but with this dog...
...it was different
because it was special.
It followed him everywhere.
They walked together through
the quarry and the forest
to the factory.
On this particular day...
...the man was to do tunnel
work,
so he said to the dog: "Stay
here."
"Stay."
The dog sat down, and it stayed.
"Good dog," the man said.
"Good dog."
And he went underground.
What the dog didn't know was
that,
on that day, the tunnel
collapsed.
Many workers died,
among them its owner.
The dog sat there and waited.
But nothing happened.
The man didn't come back up.
The other workers
tried to make the dog go home,
but it wouldn't.
It became aggressive.
So they left it there.
And there it sat.
It didn't eat anything
or drink anything.
And after a few days
it lied down
and a few days later
it stopped breathing.
My father told me that story.
I don't know...
...what to make of it.
How about you?
No.
Sometimes I don't quite know...
...what's right.
I don't always understand...
Kinda like with this story.
Do you understand?
- Get lost. And stay away.
- But Daniel, I work...
Emil!
...within the hour,
or I'll find another supplier.
Emil.
Are you sleeping?
I'll randomly shuffle this pile.
You get to decide if I shuffle
with more or fewer cards.
Okay.
- So more or fewer cards?
- More.
- Like this?
- Uh... yes.
A few more.
- Can I pick just one card?
- Like this?
- Yes, like that.
- You can have whatever you want.
- Are we done? You decide.
- Okay, then we're done.
So the police throw each group
of people into each their cell -
- so that there won't be any
trouble.
- How did you do that?
- I'm not exactly sure.
- It's great.
- Thanks.
It's magic.
I want to show you one that I
think you'll really like. Okay?
- Yes.
- Sure?
Yes.
- You'd better put these on.
- Is it dangerous?
Could be.
Careful...
- What now?
- Shh.
Starring